Guide to the Alumni Records Office, Yale University, Records of Alumni from the Classes of 1701-1978
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Alumni Records Office, Yale University, records of alumni from the Classes of 1701-1978
1868-2006
RU 830
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
1561.5
(1253 boxes)
The records consist of biographical information about Yale graduates and non-graduates from the Classes of 1701-1978. Files on individual alumni may contain addresses, freshman registration forms, obituaries, newspaper clippings, and correspondence. Also included are informational cards documenting occupations, places of employment, other degrees, accomplishments, spouses, and children.
Yale University. Alumni Records Office
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 8-B (YRG 8-B), Records on individual Yale alumni.
Conditions Governing Access
Alumni records are restricted for 75 years from the last known date of attendance.
Scope and Contents
The series have varied filing schemes for graduate and non-graduate files, and the type of degree received.
Graduates and Non-Graduates. In general, non-graduate files are identified with an "x" either before or after the year of graduation. In some sections, graduate and non-graduate files in the same class are filed together in alphabetical order. In other sections, the non-graduate files follow the graduate files of the same class. In still other sections, the non-graduate files are kept completely separate from the chronological sequence of the graduate files. If a file is not found in the graduate section, make sure to also check among the non-graduate files.
Type of Degree. In some sections, graduate files with different types of degrees are interfiled according to their class. In other sections, graduate files with different types of degrees are filed separately with their own chronological sequence.
The following explanations for each series will show the varied treatment of files for graduates and non-graduates, and different types of degrees. The explanations should be used in conjunction with the box list.
Arrangement
The records are arranged in eleven series: I. Yale College. II. Sheffield Scientific School. III. School of Medicine. IV. Law School. V. Divinity School. VI. Graduate School of Arts & Science. VII. School of Nursing. VIII. Honorary Degrees. IX. School of Music. X. Art and Architecture XI. School of Forestry and Environmental Studies; and in subsequent accessions.
Appendix: Codes Used for Fine Arts Degrees List
bfa-a Bachelor of Fine Arts in Architecture
bfa-d Bachelor of Fine Arts in Drama
bfa-p Bachelor of Fine Arts in Painting
bfa-s Bachelor of Fine Arts in Sculpture
mfa-a Master of Fine Arts in Architecture
mfa-d Master of Fine Arts in Drama
mfa-g Master of Fine Arts in Graphic Design
mfa-p Master of Fine Arts in Painting
mfa-s Master of Fine Arts in Sculpture
dfa-d Doctor of Fine Arts in Drama
cart, artc Art Certificate
cdr Drama Certificate
b-arch Bachelor of Architecture
m-arch Master of Architecture
c-arch Certificate of Architecture
mcp Master of City Planning
murs Master of Urban Studies
-aa Non-graduate, Architecture
-acp Non-graduate, City Planning
-ad Non-graduate, Drama
-ap Non-graduate, Painting
-as Non-graduate, Sculpture
Universities and colleges -- Alumni and alumnae; Yale University -- Alumni and alumnae; Yale University. Alumni Records Office
- Yale College, Series I
  Scope and Contents
  Each class (1701 to 1949) is divided into two sections for graduate and non-graduate files. Files for non-graduates follow the graduates of the same class. For example, the file for "Joe Smith, x1902" would be found in Box 159 in the 1902 non-graduate section directly after the files for the 1902 graduates. [Boxes 1-619].
  For the Classes 1950 to 1954, files for non-graduates and graduates are filed together according to their class. [Boxes 620-633]
  - 1701-1791 (Box 1)
  - 1792-1796 (Box 1A)
  - 1797-1833 (Box 2)
  - 1834-1846 (Box 3)
  - 1846-1852 (Box 4)
  - 1853 A-T (Box 5)
  - 1853 W-Z - 1855 A-L (Box 6)
  - 1855 M-Z - 1856 A-Z (Box 7)
  - x1856 A-Z - 1858 A-W (Box 8)
  - x1858 X-Z - x1859 A-Z (Box 9)
  - 1860 A-Z - 1861 A-B (Box 10)
  - 1861 C-Z - 1862 A-H (Box 11)
  - 1862 J-Z - 1863 A-L (Box 12)
  - 1863 M-Z - 1864 A-K (Box 13)
  - 1864 L-Z - 1865 A-C (Box 14)
  - 1865 D-Z - 1866 A-B (Box 15)
  - 1866 C-Z - x1866 A-Z (Box 16)
  - 1867 A-Z (Box 17)
  - x1867 A-Z - 1868 A-L (Box 18)
  - 1868 M-Z - x1868 A-T (Box 19)
  - x1868 U-Z - 1869 A-S (Box 20)
  - 1869 T-Z - 1870 A-G (Box 21)
  - 1870 H-Z (Box 22)
  - x1870 A-Z - 1871 A-L (Box 23)
  - 1871 M-Z - 1872 A-Cl (Box 24)
  - 1872 Co-R (Box 25)
  - 1872 S-Z - 1873 A-C (Box 26)
  - 1873 D-Sh (Box 27)
  - 1873 Sp-Z - 1873 A-C (Box 28)
  - 1874 F-S (Box 29)
  - 1874 T-Z - 1875 A-G (Box 30)
  - 1875 H-Z - 1876 A-Be (Box 31)
  - 1876 Bi-K (Box 32)
  - 1876 L-Z - 1877 A-B (Box 33)
  - 1877 C-R (Box 34)
  - 1877 S-Z - x1878 A-Cl (Box 35)
  - 1878 Co-Sn (Box 36)
  - 1878 Sp-Z - x1878 A-S (Box 37)
  - x1878 T-Z - 1879 A-L (Box 38)
  - 1879 M-Z - x1879 A-B (Box 39)
  - x1879 C-Z - 1880 A-G (Box 40)
  - 1880 H-S (Box 41)
  - 1880 T-Z - 1881 A-Bra (Box 42)
  - 1881 Bre-Ha (Box 43)
  - 1881 He-V (Box 44)
  - 1881 W-Z - 1882 A-B (Box 45)
  - 1882 C-R (Box 46)
  - 1882 S-R -1883 A-Bo (Box 47)
  - 1883 Bu-Ho (Box 48)
  - 1883 Hu-V (Box 49)
  - 1883 W-Z - 1884 A-E (Box 50)
  - 1884 F-Pe (Box 51)
  - 1884 Pl-Z - x1884 A-Z (Box 52)
  - 1885 A-Cross (Box 53)
  - 1885 Cross-O (Box 54)
  - 1885 P-Z - 1886 A-Ad (Box 55)
  - 1886 Al-E (Box 56)
  - 1886 F-R (Box 57)
  - 1886 S-Z - 1887 A (Box 58)
  - 1887 B-C (Box 59)
  - 1887 D-J (Box 60)
  - 1887 K-Pe (Box 61)
  - 1887 Ph-Pr (Box 62)
  - 1887 R-W (Box 63)
  - 1887 Y-Z - 1888 A-Cl (Box 64)
  - 1888 Co-L (Box 65)
  - 1888 M-Sti (Box 66)
  - 1888 Sto-Z - 1889 A-B (Box 67)
  - 1889 Br-J (Box 68)
  - 1889 K-R (Box 69)
  - 1889 S-Z - x1889 A-F (Box 70)
  - x1889 G-Z - 1890 A-B (Box 71)
  - 1890 C-Ha (Box 72)
  - 1890 Hi-Mi (Box 73)
  - 1890 Mo-S (Box 74)
  - 1890 T-Z - 1891 A (Box 75)
  - 1891 B-Dat (Box 76)
  - 1891 Dav-I (Box 77)
  - 1891 J-P (Box 78)
  - 1891 R-T (Box 79)
  - 1891 W-Z -1892 A-Ba (Box 80)
  - 1892 Bi-Gra (Box 81)
  - 1892 Gra-Man (Box 82)
  - 1892 Man-S (Box 83)
  - 1892 T-Z -1893 A (Box 84)
  - 1893 B-F (Box 85)
  - 1893 G-Me (Box 86)
  - 1893 Mi-S (Box 87)
  - 1893 T-Z - 1894 A-An (Box 88)
  - 1894 Ar-Di (Box 89)
  - 1894 Do-Holt (Box 90)
  - 1894 Holter-M (Box 91)
  - 1894 N-Sn (Box 92)
  - 1894 So-Z - x1894 A-H (Box 93)
  - 1894 I-Z - 1895 A-B (Box 94)
  - 1895 C-G (Box 95)
  - 1895 H-L (Box 96)
  - 1895 M-Q (Box 97)
  - 1895 R-V (Box 98)
  - 1895 W-Z - 1896 A-Ad (Box 99)
  - 1896 Al-B (Box 100)
  - 1896 C-Da (Box 101)
  - 1896 De-G (Box 102)
  - 1896 H-K (Box 103)
  - 1896 L-Rob (Box 104)
  - 1896 Roc-Thom (Box 105)
  - 1896 Thor-Z - x1896 A-G (Box 106)
  - x1896 H-Z - 1897 A-Bre (Box 107)
  - 1897 Bri-C (Box 108)
  - 1897 D-G (Box 109)
  - 1897 H-I (Box 110)
  - 1897 Ja-Ma (Box 111)
  - 1897 Me-Ri (Box 112)
  - 1897 Ro-V (Box 113)
  - 1897 W-Z - 1898 A-Ad (Box 114)
  - 1898 Al-Bl (Box 115)
  - 1898 Bo-C (Box 116)
  - 1898 D-Gall (Box 117)
  - 1898 Galt-H (Box 118)
  - 1898 I-Ma (Box 119)
  - 1898 Me-Ri (Box 120)
  - 1898 Ro-T (Box 121)
  - 1898 V-Z (Box 122)
  - x1898 A-Z - 1899 A (Box 123)
  - 1899 B-C (Box 124)
  - 1899 D-Gi (Box 125)
  - 1899 Go-J (Box 126)
  - 1899 K-N (Box 127)
  - 1899 O-Sto (Box 128)
  - 1899 Str-Wh (Box 129)
  - 1899 Wi-Z - 1900 A-Bak (Box 130)
  - 1900 Bar-Cl (Box 131)
  - 1900 Co-F (Box 132)
  - 1900 G-I (Box 133)
  - 1900 J-Mac (Box 134)
  - 1900 Mal-R (Box 135)
  - 1900 S-T (Box 136)
  - 1900 U-Z - x1900 A-Z (Box 137)
  - 1901 A-B (Box 138)
  - 1901 C-E (Box 139)
  - 1901 F-J (Box 140)
  - 1901 K-M (Box 141)
  - 1901 N-S (Box 142)
  - 1901 T-Wh (Box 143)
  - 1901 Wi-Z - 1902 General (Box 144)
  - 1902 General, A-Ad (Box 145)
  - 1902 Al-Br (Box 146)
  - 1902 Bu-Cor (Box 147)
  - 1902 Cor-Dr (Box 148)
  - 1902 Du-F (Box 149)
  - 1902 G-Ha (Box 150)
  - 1902 He-Hz (Box 151)
  - 1902 J-Lo (Box 152)
  - 1902 Lu-N (Box 153)
  - 1902 O-R (Box 154)
  - 1902 S-Sto (Box 155)
  - 1902 Stu-V (Box 156)
  - 1902 W-Wright (Box 157)
  - 1902 Wright-Z - x1902 A-C (Box 158)
  - x1902 D-Z - 1903 General (Box 159)
  - 1903 A-Bi (Box 160)
  - 1903 Bl-Con (Box 161)
  - 1903 Cor-E (Box 162)
  - 1903 F-Ha (Box 163)
  - 1903 He-Le (Box 164)
  - 1903 Li-M (Box 165)
  - 1903 N-Sa (Box 166)
  - 1903 Sc-Th (Box 167)
  - 1903 Ti-Z - x1903 A-B (Box 168)
  - x1903 C-Z - 1904 A-Al (Box 169)
  - 1904 An-Cha (Box 170)
  - 1904 Chi-E (Box 171)
  - 1904 F-H (Box 172)
  - 1904 I-Men (Box 173)
  - 1904 Mer-Pa (Box 174)
  - 1904 Pe-Si (Box 175)
  - 1904 Sl-V (Box 176)
  - 1904 W-Z - x1904 A-H (Box 177)
  - x1904 I-Z - 1905 A-Ar (Box 178)
  - 1905 As-B (Box 179)
  - 1905 C-E (Box 180)
  - 1905 F-Ha (Box 181)
  - 1905 He-K (Box 182)
  - 1905 L-N (Box 183)
  - 1905 O-R (Box 184)
  - 1905 S-St (Box 185)
  - 1905 Su-W (Box 186)
  - 1905 Y-Z - x1905 A-Z (Box 187)
  - 1906 A-Ba (Box 188)
  - 1906 Be-Co (Box 189)
  - 1906 Cr-E (Box 190)
  - 1906 F-G (Box 191)
  - 1906 H-J (Box 192)
  - 1906 K-Mac (Box 193)
  - 1906 Mag-O (Box 194)
  - 1906 P-R (Box 195)
  - 1906 S (Box 196)
  - 1906 T-We (Box 197)
  - 1906 Wh-Z - x1906 A-Ba (Box 198)
  - x1906 Br-Z - 1907 General (Box 199)
  - 1907 General, A-Bi (Box 200)
  - 1907 Bl-Cl (Box 201)
  - 1907 Co-Do (Box 202)
  - 1907 Dr-G (Box 203)
  - 1907 H (Box 204)
  - 1907 J-Leo (Box 205)
  - 1907 Lew-Mac (Box 206)
  - 1907 Mad-N (Box 207)
  - 1907 O-Q (Box 208)
  - 1907 R-Sn (Box 209)
  - 1907 So-Th (Box 210)
  - 1907 To-Wh (Box 211)
  - 1907 Wi-Z - x1907 A-H (Box 212)
  - x1907 I-Z - 1908 A-Ad (Box 213)
  - 1908 Al-Ben (Box 214)
  - 1908 Ber-Bz (Box 215)
  - 1908 C-Da (Box 216)
  - 1908 De-F (Box 217)
  - 1908 G-Hi (Box 218)
  - 1908 Ho-J (Box 219)
  - 1908 K-Mac (Box 220)
  - 1908 Mal-N (Box 221)
  - 1908 O-P (Box 222)
  - 1908 R-Sey (Box 223)
  - 1908 Sey-Smi (Box 224)
  - 1908 Smi-T (Box 225)
  - 1908 U-Z (Box 226)
  - x1908 A-Z (Box 227)
  - 1909 A-Ba (Box 228)
  - 1909 Be-Ch (Box 229)
  - 1909 Cl-D (Box 230)
  - 1909 E-Ha (Box 231)
  - 1909 He-Ke (Box 232)
  - 1909 Ki-Mac (Box 233)
  - 1909 Mar-Ph (Box 234)
  - 1909 Pl-Sc (Box 235)
  - 1909 Se-V (Box 236)
  - 1909 W-Z - x1909 A-O (Box 237)
  - x1909 P-Z - 1910 A-Bak (Box 238)
  - 1910 Bar-Bz (Box 239)
  - 1910 C-Di (Box 240)
  - 1910 Dr-Gi (Box 241)
  - 1910 Gl-Ho (Box 242)
  - 1910 Hs-L (Box 243)
  - 1910 M-N (Box 244)
  - 1910 O-R (Box 245)
  - 1910 S-Taft (Box 246)
  - 1910 Tan-Z - x1910 A-B (Box 247)
  - x1910 C-Z - 1911 General (Box 248)
  - 1911 General, A-Broc (Box 249)
  - 1911 Brow-Dar (Box 250)
  - 1911 Dav-Fo (Box 251)
  - 1911 Fr-Ha (Box 252)
  - 1911 He-I (Box 253)
  - 1911 J-Lo (Box 254)
  - 1911 Lu-O (Box 255)
  - 1911 P-Se (Box 256)
  - 1911 Sh-V (Box 257)
  - 1911 W-Z - x1911 A-D (Box 258)
  - 1911 E-Z - 1912 A (Box 259)
  - 1912 B (Box 260)
  - 1912 C-D (Box 261)
  - 1912 E-G (Box 262)
  - 1912 H-K (Box 263)
  - 1912 L-M (Box 264)
  - 1912 N-R (Box 265)
  - 1912 S-V (Box 266)
  - 1912 W-Z - x1912 A-H (Box 267)
  - x1912 I-Z - 1913 General (Box 268)
  - 1913 A-Ba (Box 269)
  - 1913 Be-Bz (Box 270)
  - 1913 C-Co (Box 271)
  - 1913 Cr-D (Box 272)
  - 1913 E-Ga (Box 273)
  - 1913 Gi-Har (Box 274)
  - 1913 Harp-Hz (Box 275)
  - 1913 I-L (Box 276)
  - 1913 M (Box 277)
  - 1913 N-Po (Box 278)
  - 1913 Pr-R (Box 279)
  - 1913 S (Box 280)
  - 1913 T-Wa (Box 281)
  - 1913 We-Z (Box 282)
  - x1913 A-Z (Box 283)
  - 1914 A-Be (Box 284)
  - 1914 Bi-Co (Box 285)
  - 1914 Cr-F (Box 286)
  - 1914 G-I (Box 287)
  - 1914 J-L (Box 288)
  - 1914 M-Pa (Box 289)
  - 1914 Pe-Se (Box 290)
  - 1914 Sh-T (Box 291)
  - 1914 U-Z - x1914 A-P (Box 292)
  - x1914 R-Z - 1915 A-Al (Box 293)
  - 1915 Ar-B (Box 294)
  - 1915 C-Da (Box 295)
  - 1915 D-Gl (Box 296)
  - 1915 Go-K (Box 297)
  - 1915 L-Me (Box 298)
  - 1915 Mi-Ra (Box 299)
  - 1915 Re-Stei (Box 300)
  - 1915 Stew-We (Box 301)
  - 1915 Wh-Z - x1915 A-P (Box 302)
  - x1915 R-Z - 1916 A (Box 303)
  - 1916 B (Box 304)
  - 1916 C-Di (Box 305)
  - 1916 Do-Go (Box 306)
  - 1916 Gr-H (Box 307)
  - 1916 I-L (Box 308)
  - 1916 M-O (Box 309)
  - 1916 P-R (Box 310)
  - 1916 S-T (Box 311)
  - 1916 U-Z - x1916 A-B (Box 312)
  - x1916 C-S (Box 313)
  - x1916 T-Z - 1917 A-An (Box 314)
  - 1917 Ar-Bur (Box 315)
  - 1917 Bus-Co (Box 316)
  - 1917 Cr-E (Box 317)
  - 1917 F-Ha (Box 318)
  - 1917 He-J (Box 319)
  - 1917 K-Mac (Box 320)
  - 1917 Mar-Phe (Box 321)
  - 1917 Phi-Sh (Box 322)
  - 1917 Si-Ti (Box 323)
  - 1917 To-Z (Box 324)
  - x1917 A-T (Box 325)
  - x1917 U-Z - 1918 General (Box 326)
  - 1918 A-Bi (Box 327)
  - 1918 Bu-Co (Box 328)
  - 1918 Cu-Dr (Box 329)
  - 1918 Du-Gr (Box 330)
  - 1918 Gu-Ho (Box 331)
  - 1918 Hu-K (Box 332)
  - 1918 L-Mc (Box 333)
  - 1918 Ma-Par (Box 334)
  - 1918 Pat-R (Box 335)
  - 1918 S-So (Box 336)
  - 1918 Sp-V (Box 337)
  - 1918 W-Z - x1918 A-B (Box 338)
  - x1918 C-P (Box 339)
  - x1918 R-Z (Box 340)
  - 1919 A (Box 341)
  - 1919 B-Bo (Box 342)
  - 1919 Br-C (Box 343)
  - 1919 D-F (Box 344)
  - 1919 G-Ha (Box 345)
  - 1919 He-Lo (Box 346)
  - 1919 Lu-Mo (Box 347)
  - 1919 Mu-Ri (Box 348)
  - 1919 Ru-Sm (Box 349)
  - 1919 She-Wil (Box 350)
  - 1919 Woo-Z - x1919 A-D (Box 351)
  - x1919 E-N (Box 352)
  - x1919 Pa-Z (Box 353)
  - 1920 A-Bro (Box 354)
  - 1920 Bru-D (Box 355)
  - 1920 E-Ha (Box 356)
  - 1920 Hc-K (Box 357)
  - 1920 L-O (Box 358)
  - 1920 P-S (Box 359)
  - 1920 T-W (Box 360)
  - 1920 XYZ - x1920 A-F (Box 361)
  - x1920 G-P (Box 362)
  - x1920 R-Z - 1921 General (Box 363)
  - 1921 A-Chi (Box 364)
  - 1921 Cla-Hal (Box 365)
  - 1921 Han-J (Box 366)
  - 1921 K-Mal (Box 367)
  - 1921 Mar-R (Box 368)
  - 1921 S-War (Box 369)
  - 1921 Wat-Z - x1921 A-J (Box 370)
  - x1921 K-Z - 1922 A-Al (Box 371)
  - 1922 And-B (Box 372)
  - 1922 C-D (Box 373)
  - 1922 E-Har (Box 374)
  - 1922 He-Lord (Box 375)
  - 1922 Lord - Pax (Box 376)
  - 1922 Pei-Ste (Box 377)
  - 1922 Sto-W (Box 378)
  - 1922 XYZ - x1922 A-Mey (Box 379)
  - x1922 Mil-Z (Box 380)
  - 1923 A-Ber (Box 381)
  - 1923 Big-Col (Box 382)
  - 1923 Com-Des (Box 383)
  - 1923 Dol-F (Box 384)
  - 1923 Gar-Hir (Box 385)
  - 1923 Hol-Mars (Box 386)
  - 1923 Mart-P (Box 387)
  - 1923 Q-S (Box 388)
  - 1923 T-Z (Box 389)
  - x1923 A-E (Box 390)
  - x1923 F-U (Box 391)
  - x1923 U-Z - 1924 A-Bla (Box 392)
  - 1924 Boa-E (Box 393)
  - 1924 F-Hua (Box 394)
  - 1924 Hub-Mar (Box 395)
  - 1924 Mee-R (Box 396)
  - 1924 S-V (Box 397)
  - 1924 W-Z - x1924 A-J (Box 398)
  - x1924 K-Z - 1925 General (Box 399)
  - 1925 General-Bou (Box 400)
  - 1925 Bow-C (Box 401)
  - 1925 D-Ge (Box 402)
  - 1925 Gi-Hoo (Box 403)
  - 1925 Hop-K (Box 404)
  - 1925 L-Me (Box 405)
  - 1925 Mil-Pop (Box 406)
  - 1925 Pos-Ros (Box 407)
  - 1925 Rot-Smith, E. (Box 408)
  - 1925 Smith, J.-Whi (Box 409)
  - 1925 Wie-Z x1925 A-McB (Box 410)
  - x1925 McM-V (Box 411)
  - 1926 A-Bon (Box 412)
  - 1926 Bow-Cra (Box 413)
  - 1926 Cre-F (Box 414)
  - 1926 G-H (Box 415)
  - 1926 I-Loo (Box 416)
  - 1926 Lor-Nor (Box 417)
  - 1926 O-Roc (Box 418)
  - 1926 Roe-Sto (Box 419)
  - 1926 Stoe-W (Box 420)
  - 1926 X-Z - x1926 A-H (Box 421)
  - x1926 J-W (Box 422)
  - 1927 A-Big (Box 423)
  - 1927 Bin-Coa (Box 424)
  - 1927 Coh-E (Box 425)
  - 1927 F-Ham (Box 426)
  - 1927 Han-K (Box 427)
  - 1927 L-Mes (Box 428)
  - 1927 Mi-Po (Box 429)
  - 1927 Pr-Smi (Box 430)
  - 1927 Sol-Val (Box 431)
  - 1927 Van-Z - x1927 A-C (Box 432)
  - x1927 D-Sl (Box 433)
  - x1927 Sn-Z - 1928 A-Bar (Box 434)
  - 1928 Bas-Cal (Box 435)
  - 1928 Cam-Cut (Box 436)
  - 1928 D-F (Box 437)
  - 1928 G-Hod (Box 438)
  - 1928 Hof-K (Box 439)
  - 1928 L-Mar (Box 440)
  - 1928 Mr-Pa (Box 441)
  - 1928 Pe-Sa (Box 442)
  - 1928 Sc-Th (Box 443)
  - 1928 To-Z (Box 444)
  - x1928 A-R (Box 445)
  - x1928 S-Z - 1929 A-Ba (Box 446)
  - 1929 Bak-But (Box 447)
  - 1929 C-Def (Box 448)
  - 1929 Dic-F (Box 449)
  - 1929 G-Hit (Box 450)
  - 1929 Hoc-Kos (Box 451)
  - 1929 Kra-Mat (Box 452)
  - 1929 Mel-Pet (Box 453)
  - 1929 Pi-Sil (Box 454)
  - 1929 Sim-T (Box 455)
  - 1929 U-Woo (Box 456)
  - 1929 Wri-Z - x1929 A-J (Box 457)
  - x1929 K-Z (Box 458)
  - 1930 General, A-Ba (Box 459)
  - 1930 Be-Ci (Box 460)
  - 1930 Cl-El (Box 461)
  - 1930 Em-Go (Box 462)
  - 1930 Gr-Ha (Box 463)
  - 1930 He-Ki (Box 464)
  - 1930 Kl-Mah (Box 465)
  - 1930 Mat-N (Box 466)
  - 1930 O-Ri (Box 467)
  - 1930 Ro-Sn (Box 468)
  - 1930 So-V (Box 469)
  - 1930 W-Z - x1930 A-B (Box 470)
  - x1930 C-R (Box 471)
  - x1930 S-Z - 1931 A-Ba (Box 472)
  - 1931 Be-Ca (Box 473)
  - 1931 Ce-Di (Box 474)
  - 1931 Do-Ga (Box 475)
  - 1931 Ge-Hi (Box 476)
  - 1931 Ho-La (Box 477)
  - 1931 Le-Mag (Box 478)
  - 1931 Mah-Pa (Box 479)
  - 1931 Pe-R (Box 480)
  - 1931 S (Box 481)
  - 1931 T-Wh (Box 482)
  - 1931 Wi-Z - x1931 A-J (Box 483)
  - x1931 K-Z - 1932 General (Box 484)
  - 1932 A-Bl (Box 485)
  - 1932 Bo-Co (Box 486)
  - 1932 Cr-Fi (Box 487)
  - 1932 Fl-Hal (Box 488)
  - 1932 Ham-La (Box 489)
  - 1932 Le-Mi (Box 490)
  - 1932 Mo-P (Box 491)
  - 1932 Q-St (Box 492)
  - 1932 Su-Z (Box 493)
  - x1932 A-V (Box 494)
  - x1932 W-Z - 1933 General, A (Box 495)
  - 1933 B-Ce (Box 496)
  - 1933 Ch-Do (Box 497)
  - 1933 Du-G (Box 498)
  - 1933 H-J (Box 499)
  - 1933 K-Ma (Box 500)
  - 1933 Me-Pl (Box 501)
  - 1933 Po-Si (Box 502)
  - 1933 Sk-Wal (Box 503)
  - 1933 Wam-Z - x1933 A-E (Box 504)
  - x1933 F-Z (Box 505)
  - 1934 General, A-Bor (Box 506)
  - 1934 Bos-C (Box 507)
  - 1934 D-G (Box 508)
  - 1934 H-Ki (Box 509)
  - 1934 Kl-Mi (Box 510)
  - 1934 Mo-Sc (Box 511)
  - 1934 Se-V (Box 512)
  - 1934 W-Z - x1934 A-B (Box 513)
  - x1934 C-R (Box 514)
  - x1934 S-Z - 1935 General, A-B (Box 515)
  - 1935 Be-Cok (Box 516)
  - 1935 Col-E (Box 517)
  - 1935 F-Ho (Box 518)
  - 1935 Hu-L - Mac-Mc (Box 519)
  - 1935 M-Ri (Box 520)
  - 1935 Ro-S (Box 521)
  - 1935 T-Whe (Box 522)
  - 1935 Whi-Z - x1935 A-L (Box 523)
  - x1935 M-Z - 1936 General, A (Box 524)
  - 1936 B (Box 525)
  - 1936 C-Dr (Box 526)
  - 1936 Dv-Hen (Box 527)
  - 1936 Her-La (Box 528)
  - 1936 Le-N (Box 529)
  - 1936 O-Rog (Box 530)
  - 1936 Ros-Th (Box 531)
  - 1936 Ti-Z - x1936 A-Ch (Box 532)
  - x1936 Ci-Z (Box 533)
  - 1937 General, A-Bo (Box 534)
  - 1937 Br-Di (Box 535)
  - 1937 Do-Go (Box 536)
  - 1937 Gr-Ka (Box 537)
  - 1937 Ke-Ma (Box 538)
  - 1937 Me-Ri (Box 539)
  - 1937 Ro-T (Box 540)
  - 1937 U-Z - x1937 A-F (Box 541)
  - x1937 G-Z (Box 542)
  - 1938 General, A-B (Box 543)
  - 1938 C-E (Box 544)
  - 1938 F-H (Box 545)
  - 1938 I-Mi (Box 546)
  - 1938 Mo-She (Box 547)
  - 1938 Sher-Wem (Box 548)
  - 1938 Wen-Z - x1938 A-M (Box 549)
  - x1938 P-Z (Box 550)
  - 1939 A-Br (Box 551)
  - 1939 Bu-D (Box 552)
  - 1939 E-He (Box 553)
  - 1939 Hi-L (Box 554)
  - 1939 M-P (Box 555)
  - 1939 R-St (Box 556)
  - 1939 Su-W - x1939 A-B (Box 557)
  - x1939 C-Z (Box 558)
  - 1940 A-Br (Box 559)
  - 1940 Bu-D (Box 560)
  - 1940 E-He (Box 561)
  - 1940 Hi-L (Box 562)
  - 1940 M-Pl (Box 563)
  - 1940 Po-S (Box 564)
  - 1940 T-Wi (Box 565)
  - 1940 Wo-Z - x1940 A-P (Box 566)
  - x1940 R-Z - 1941 A-Be (Box 567)
  - 1941 Bi-Do (Box 568)
  - 1941 Dr-Hi (Box 569)
  - 1941 Ho-Mac (Box 570)
  - 1941 Mad-Re (Box 571)
  - 1941 Ri-V (Box 572)
  - 1941 W-Z - x1941 A-C (Box 573)
  - x1941 M-Z - 1942 A-Be (Box 574)
  - 1942 Bi-Do (Box 575)
  - 1942 Du-I (Box 576)
  - 1942 J-N (Box 577)
  - 1942 O-Sm (Box 578)
  - 1942 So-Z - x1942 A-E (Box 579)
  - x1942 F-Z - 1943 A-Be (Box 580)
  - 1943 Bi-D (Box 581)
  - 1943 E-H (Box 582)
  - 1943 I-M (Box 583)
  - 1943 N-S (Box 584)
  - 1943 T-Z - x1943 A-Mc (Box 585)
  - x1943 Mo-Z - 1944 A-Br (Box 586)
  - 1944 Bu-Fi (Box 587)
  - 1944 Fl-Lin (Box 588)
  - 1944 Lit-R (Box 589)
  - 1944 S-We (Box 590)
  - 1944 Wh-Z - x1944 (Box 591)
  - 1945 A-Com (Box 592)
  - 1945 Con-Haw (Box 593)
  - 1945 Hoy-Mo (Box 594)
  - 1945 Mu-Su (Box 595)
  - 1945 Sw-Z - x1945 A-F (Box 596)
  - x1945 G-Z - 1945W A-Bi (Box 597)
  - 1945W Bl-F (Box 598)
  - 1945W G-Mar (Box 599)
  - 1945W Mas-S (Box 600)
  - 1945W T-Z - x1945W A-Go (Box 601)
  - x1945W Gr-Z (Box 602)
  - 1946 A-Mar (Box 603)
  - 1946 Mas-Z - x1946 A-L (Box 604)
  - x1946 M-Z - 1947 A-Bo (Box 605)
  - 1947 Br-He (Box 606)
  - 1947 Hi-R (Box 607)
  - 1947 S-Z - x1947 A-Mc (Box 608)
  - x1947 Mi-Z - 1948 A-Co (Box 609)
  - 1948 Cr-H (Box 610)
  - 1948 Ho-Mu (Box 611)
  - 1948 My-St (Box 612)
  - 1948 Su-Z - 1948x (Box 613)
  - 1949 (General Info) - Averback (Box 613A)
  - 1949 B-Di (Box 614)
  - 1949 Do-Ho (Box 615)
  - 1949 Hu-M (Box 616)
  - 1949 N-Ste (Box 617)
  - 1949 Sti-Z - x1949 A-Z (Box 618)
  - 1949x A-Z (Box 619)
  - 1950 A-C (Box 620)
  - 1950 D-H (Box 621)
  - 1950 I-N (Box 622)
  - 1950 O-V (Box 623)
  - 1950 W-Z, 1951 A-Di (Box 624)
  - 1951 Do-L (Box 625)
  - 1951 M-Vann (Box 626)
  - 1951 Vau-Z, 1952 A-Ga (Box 627)
  - 1952 Ge-U (Box 628)
  - 1952 V-Z, 1953 A-F (Box 629)
  - 1953 G-P (Box 630)
  - 1953 Q-Z, 1954 A-Cl (Box 631)
  - 1954 Co-Se (Box 632)
  - 1954 Sh-Z (Box 633)
- Sheffield Scientific School and Engineering, Series II
  Classes 1849 to 1945 contain files for Sheffield and Engineering graduates and non-graduates. Even though Sheffield became part of Yale College in 1935, the alumni records for Sheffield were still kept separately. Each class is divided into two sections for graduates and non-graduates. Non-graduates follow the graduates of the same class. For example, the file for "Joe Smith, x1902 s" would be found in box 694 in the 1902 non-graduate section directly after the files for the 1902 graduates. [Boxes 634-904]
  For the Class of 1945 (with degrees We and Ws), files for non-graduates follow the graduates of the same class. [Boxes 904-907]
  For the Class of 1946, files for non-graduates follow the graduates of the same class. [Boxes 907-909]
  The files for the Class of 1946 with the Mar E&S degree are in Box 909.
  For the Classes of 1947-1950, Undergraduate Engineering, files for non-graduates follow the graduates of the same class. [Boxes 910-914]
  Files for students graduating from 1936 to 1949 with the Doctorate of Engineering (D.Eng.) are filed as a separate group. [Box 915]
  Files for students graduating from 1936 to 1949 with the Master of Engineering (M.Eng.) are filed as a separate group. [Boxes 915-916]
  Files for students graduating from 1936 to 1949 with miscellaneous engineering degrees (Misc. Degree) are filed as a separate group. [Boxes 916-917]
  - Special file A-U (Box 634)
  - Special file V-Z 1849-1867 (Box 635)
  - 1868-1871 A-S (Box 636)
  - 1871 T-Z - 1874 A-R (Box 637)
  - 1874 S-Z - 1876 A-H (Box 638)
  - 1876 I-Z - x1877 A-M (Box 639)
  - x1877 N-Z - 1879 A-B (Box 640)
  - 1879 C-Z - 1880 A-I (Box 641)
  - 1880 L-Z - 1881 A-M (Box 642)
  - 1881 O-Z - 1882 A-C (Box 643)
  - 1882 E-Z (Box 644)
  - x1882 A-Z - x1883 A-Z (Box 645)
  - 1884 A-Z - x1884 A-Z (Box 646)
  - 1885 A-Z (Box 647)
  - x1885 A-Z - 1886 A-R (Box 648)
  - 1886 S-Z - 1887 A-O (Box 649)
  - 1887 P-Z - 1888 A-F (Box 650)
  - 1888 G-Z (Box 651)
  - x1888 A-Z - 1889 A-P (Box 652)
  - 1889 Q-Z - 1890 A-K (Box 653)
  - 1890 L-Z - x1890 A-Z (Box 654)
  - 1891 A-F (Box 655)
  - 1891 G-Sh (Box 656)
  - 1891 Si-Z - x1891 A-Z (Box 657)
  - 1892 A-Ho (Box 658)
  - 1892 Hu-We (Box 659)
  - 1892 Wh-Z - 1893 A-B (Box 660)
  - 1893 C-K (Box 661)
  - 1893 L-T (Box 662)
  - 1893 U-Z - 1894 A-C (Box 663)
  - 1894 D-L (Box 664)
  - 1894 M-V (Box 665)
  - 1894 W-Z - 1895 A (Box 666)
  - 1895 B-F (Box 667)
  - 1895 G-P (Box 668)
  - 1895 Q-Z - x1895 A-G (Box 669)
  - x1895 H-Z - 1896 A-Cl (Box 670)
  - 1896 Co-I (Box 671)
  - 1896 J-Q (Box 672)
  - 1896 R-Z - x1896 A-B (Box 673)
  - x1896 C-Z - 1897 A-B (Box 674)
  - 1897 Be-E (Box 675)
  - 1897 F-Me (Box 676)
  - 1897 Mi-S (Box 677)
  - 1897 T-Z - x1897 A-Z (Box 678)
  - 1898 A-K (Box 679)
  - 1898 L-Z - x1898 A-H (Box 680)
  - x1898 I-Z - 1899 A-Cl (Box 681)
  - 1899 Co-Ha (Box 682)
  - 1899 He-T (Box 683)
  - 1899 U-Z - x1899 A-Z (Box 684)
  - 1900 A-Ha (Box 685)
  - 1900 He-Sp (Box 686)